In one small bottle... The fountain of youth. The secret of eternal life. The power
of an ancient potion. Sometimes it works... sometimes it doesn't.
Death Becomes Her is a comedy, fantasy, horror film directed by Robert Zemeckis.
Madeline is married to Ernest, who was once her arch-rival Helen's fiancé.
After recovering from a mental breakdown, Helen vows to
kill Madeline and steal back Ernest.
Unfortunately for everyone, the introduction of a magic potion causes things
to be a great deal more complicated than a mere murder plot.
Madeline Ashton Menville, played by Meryl Streep.
Helen Sharp, played by Goldie Hawn.
Dr. Ernest Menville, played by Bruce Willis.
Lisle von Rhuman, played by Isabella Rossellini.
Chagall, played by Ian Ogilvy.
Dakota, played by Adam Storke.
Death Becomes Her is a 1992 American surrealist black comedy fantasy film directed and
produced by Robert Zemeckis and written by David Koepp and Martin Donovan.
The film stars Meryl Streep, Goldie Hawn, Bruce Willis, and Isabella Rossellini.
Its plot follows two women who drink a magic potion that promises eternal youth.
Filming began in December 1991 and concluded in April
1992; it was filmed in Los Angeles.
Death Becomes Her was released in the United States by
Universal Pictures on July 31, 1992.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
It was also a pioneer in the use of computer-generated effects and went
on to win the Academy Award for Best Visual Effects.
The film is regarded as a cult classic and a highly
treasured film within the gay community.
It has since been adapted into a critically acclaimed
Tony Award-winning Broadway musical.
The film explores themes of jealousy, immortality, beauty, rivalry, potion.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.